JIHEE KIM

ASPIRING ARCHITECT



Career goal:

During and after my architectural education, I intend to explore the relationship between architectue as an active foundation to people's interactions and its navigators' experience, focusing on public buildings. It is my hope to become a licensed architect, dedicated to sustainability.

Personal

Date of birth: 17 April 1997 Citizenship: Republic of Korea

Address: 5032 Forbes Avenue, SMC 4587, Pittsburgh, PA 15289

Phone: +1 (831) 512-8772 E-mail: jiheekl@andrew.cmu.edu

LANGHAGES

LEARNING: Japanese, German

EDUCATION

CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY, PITTSBURGH PA | 08.2016 - 05.2021

Bachelor of Architecture

QPA: 3.57/4.0 (Studio QPA: 4.0/4.0)

School Honors: Fall 2016

NOTRE DAME HIGH SCHOOL, SALINAS CA | 08.2012 - 05.2016

Final GPA: 4.286/4.0

First Honors: Fall & Spring 2012-2016

SKILLS

ENGLISH



LLO ing crafting shop

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

VOLUNTEER / JOHN STEINBECK LIBRARY, SALINAS CA | 08.2014 - 05.2016

Coordinated and taught arts and crafts activities

VOLUNTEER / THE BOYS AND GIRLS CLUB, SALINAS CA | 08.2013 - 05.2014

Assisted children with arts and crafts projects

PROJECTS

CUBE HOUSE WEDDING PAVILLION ON LAKE EERIE

Architecture Design Studio: Foundation I | Fall 2016 One of the Final 6 to present work at Semester Reviews

COURSE WORK

Architecture Design Studio
Analog and Digital Media
Building Physics
Exploring Pittsburgh
Historical Survey of World Architecture and Urbanism

ACTIVITIES & LEADERSHIP

ZAIA

Member | Fall 2016 - Present

ALPHA PHI OMEGA, KAPPA CHAPTER

Member | Fall 2016 - Present Part of Spring Carnival Booth Committee

HABITAT FOR HUMANITY

Member | Fall 2016 - Present

AB Tech

Member | Spring 2017 - Present

Awards / Presentation

2015: Carol Frindt Scholarship for Excellence in Visual Arts 2014: Honorable Metion & Display at Seaside Art Show 2014: Louis Huntington, Sr. Memorial Award in Art